{
    "country": {
        "question": "For the start I have to roughly know where you live, for further consideration of course.",
        "fallback": "It is sufficient when you say if you are in or outside the european union.",
        "result": {
            "eu": [
                "germany",
                "ger",
                "de",
                "france",
                "fr",
                "spain",
                "portugal",
                "austria",
                "belgium",
                "croatia",
                "denmark",
                "estonia",
                "finland",
                "greece",
                "hungary",
                "island",
                "ireland",
                "italy",
                "luxembourg",
                "netherlands",
                "sweden",
                "eu",
                "europe",
                "union"
            ],
            "no_eu": [
                "america",
                "africa",
                "any",
                "asia",
                "suisse",
                "australia"
            ]
        }
    },
    "license": {
        "question": "Do you already have a licence registered in the EU? And if yes which?",
        "fallback": "The valid options are A1, A2, A3 or none!",
        "result": {
            "none": [
                "no ",
                "dont",
                "n't",
                "never",
                "negative",
                "false"
            ],
            "A1": [
                "minor",
                "a1",
                "500"
            ],
            "A2": [
                "normal",
                "a2",
                "2,5",
                "2.5",
                "2500"
            ],
            "A3": [
                "big",
                "major",
                "a3",
                "25",
                "25000"
            ]
        }
    },
    "people": {
        "question": "Talking about people, where do you want to fly in regard of uninvolved people?",
        "fallback": "Do you want to fly near, over or far away from people?",
        "result": {
            "over": [
                "over",
                "crowds",
                "concert",
                "town",
                "urban",
                "groups"
            ],
            "close": [
                "near",
                "next",
                "close",
                "sports",
                "around"
            ],
            "away": [
                "far",
                "forest",
                "willow",
                "away",
                "remote",
                "isolated",
                "secure",
                "distance"
            ]
        }
    },
    "location": {
        "question": "Depending on your flight area some drones may be more useful, so what is your flight territory?",
        "fallback": "Where do you fly, indoors or outdoors?",
        "result": {
            "outdoor": [
                "outdoor",
                "outside",
                "free",
                "air",
                "forest",
                "field",
                "band",
                "garden",
                "away",
                "both",
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "indoor": [
                "indoor",
                "inside",
                "mine",
                "between",
                "under",
                "close",
                "tight",
                "small",
                "house",
                "through"
            ]
        }
    },
    "knowledge": {
        "question": "Which knowledge about the applicable law do you have?",
        "fallback": "How would you categorize your knowledge over your country's drone law, not existing, little, or big enough?",
        "result": {
            "none": [
                "no ",
                "dont",
                "n't",
                "never",
                "negative",
                "false"
            ],
            "little": [
                "little",
                "bit",
                "some",
                "few",
                "small"
            ],
            "enough": [
                "enough",
                "much",
                "know",
                "detail",
                "all",
                "every"
            ]
        }
    },
    "budget": {
        "question": "How much are you willing to spend on this adventure?",
        "fallback": "Please enter your answer in a common format in the unit EUR!",
        "result": false
    },
    "margin": {
        "question": "How big is your margin on top of that? No worries, I won't ask another time.",
        "fallback": "Please enter your answer in a common format in the unit EUR which is not zero!",
        "result": false
    },
    "type": {
        "question": "For what type of activity do you want to use your drone?",
        "fallback": "Please help me to fit your input into one of these categories: fun, sport or work.",
        "result": {
            "fun": [
                "fun",
                "experiment",
                "try",
                "play",
                "indoors",
                "looping",
                "foto",
                "film",
                "video"
            ],
            "sport": [
                "sport",
                "achieve",
                "push",
                "limit",
                "race",
                "explore"
            ],
            "work": [
                "work",
                "job",
                "farm",
                "find",
                "professional",
                "cinema",
                "search",
                "help",
                "rescue"
            ]
        }
    },
    "spec_type": {
        "question": "What concrete use-case do you want to satisfy with the drone?",
        "fallback": "Please specify which use the drone should have: foto/video, playing, freestyle, racing, movie shoots, agricultural work or monitoring.",
        "result": {
            "foto": [
                "film",
                "foto",
                "capture",
                "video",
                "vacation"
            ],
            "toy": [
                "play",
                "toy",
                "kid",
                "experiment",
                "looping",
                "indoors"
            ],
            "freestyle": [
                "free",
                "explore",
                "hit",
                "tricks",
                "learn",
                "find out",
                "experience"
            ],
            "race": [
                "race",
                "compete",
                "fast",
                "sport",
                "athlete"
            ],
            "movie": [
                "cinema",
                "movie",
                "quality"
            ],
            "agricultural": [
                "agri",
                "farm",
                "field",
                "spray",
                "auto"
            ],
            "monitoring": [
                "monitor",
                "find",
                "search",
                "help",
                "get",
                "rescue"
            ]
        }
    },
    "distance": {
        "question": "How far do you want to fly and explore your surrounding?",
        "fallback": "Possible options are in sight, further than your visual line, and long range (over a kilometer).",
        "result": {
            "vlos": [
                "near",
                "close",
                "side",
                "around",
                "sight"
            ],
            "bvlos": [
                "wide",
                "far",
                "away",
                "explore",
                "long",
                "range"
            ]
        }
    },
    "time": {
        "question": "In regard of this distance you want to overcome, what is your targeted airtime?",
        "fallback": "How long do you want to fly in minutes?",
        "result": {
            "short": [
                "short",
                "around",
                "1",
                "2"
            ],
            "middle": [
                "middle",
                "bit",
                "some",
                "3",
                "4",
                "5"
            ],
            "long": [
                "long",
                "around",
                "long",
                "last"
            ]
        }
    },
    "behaviour": {
        "question": "Another factor, which drastically influences your airtime is your flight style. How hard are you going to push your quad?",
        "fallback": "How would you describe your flight style, defensive, moderate or aggressive?",
        "result": {
            "defensive": [
                "defensive",
                "slow",
                "secure",
                "around",
                "look",
                "search",
                "find",
                "new",
                "check"
            ],
            "moderate": [
                "bit",
                "some",
                "moderate",
                "normal",
                "explore",
                "view",
                "tricks"
            ],
            "aggressive": [
                "aggressive",
                "fast",
                "push",
                "race",
                "crash",
                "risk"
            ]
        }
    },
    "size": {
        "question": "Drone are out there in all different sizes. What is your idea of the size of the drone?",
        "fallback": "How big should your drone be? Small, medium, large or huge...",
        "result": {
            "small": [
                "small",
                "little",
                "mini",
                "hand",
                "finger",
                "tiny",
                "1",
                "2"
            ],
            "medium": [
                "medium",
                "middle",
                "normal",
                "standard",
                "average",
                "typical",
                "general",
                "3",
                "4",
                "5"
            ],
            "large": [
                "big",
                "large",
                "arm",
                "6",
                "7",
                "8",
                "9"
            ],
            "huge": [
                "huge",
                "insane",
                "great",
                "gigantic",
                "colossal",
                "massive",
                "sit",
                "10",
                "11",
                "12"
            ]
        }
    },
    "fpv": {
        "question": "FPV - First-Person-View is an immersive experience, do you want to sit in the virtual cockpit?",
        "fallback": "Do you want the opportunity to see what the drone sees, yes or no?",
        "result": {
            "yes": [
                "yes",
                "ja",
                "ya",
                "positive",
                "true",
                "do ",
                "want"
            ],
            "no": [
                "no ",
                "dont",
                "n't",
                "never",
                "negative",
                "false"]
        }
    },
    "feed": {
        "question": "When you got a live-cam, you have to choose between quality and performance... What is your preference?",
        "fallback": "The difference between analog and digital are performance and quality, respectively, what is your choice?",
        "result": {
            "analog": [
                "analog",
                "noisy",
                "noise",
                "performance",
                "fast",
                "race",
                "speed",
                "transmission",
                "camera"
            ],
            "digital": [
                "digital",
                "clear",
                "quality",
                "image",
                "cinema",
                "latency"
            ]
        }
    },
    "automation": {
        "question": "The degree of automation is the last big question, how much should your drone can do by itself?",
        "fallback": "How automated should your drone be, not at all, minimal, normal or complete autonomous?",
        "result": {
            "none": [
                "no ",
                "dont",
                "n't",
                "never",
                "negative",
                "false"
            ],
            "minimal": [
                "mini",
                "gps",
                "almost",
                "half",
                "bit",
                "some",
                "few"
            ],
            "automated": [
                "automa",
                "gps",
                "sensors",
                "mavic",
                "dji",
                "control"
            ],
            "autonomous": [
                "itself",
                "completely",
                "all",
                "everything",
                "autono",
                "alone"
            ]
        }
    },
    "camera": {
        "question": "Additional cameras have their own flavour, do you need an extra camera, or external rig for your setup?",
        "fallback": "Extra cameras on your drone have many forms, now you have to choose between none, action-cams, normal cameras, cinematic cameras, and infrared (eg. for searches).",
        "result": {
            "none": [
                "try",
                "experiment",
                "no ",
                "dont",
                "n't",
                "never",
                "negative",
                "false"
            ],
            "action": [
                "action",
                "go",
                "pro",
                "little",
                "small",
                "tiny"
            ],
            "camera": [
                "mount",
                "events",
                "camera",
                "big",
                "film"
            ],
            "movie": [
                "movie",
                "create",
                "profession",
                "cinema"
            ],
            "infrared": [
                "search",
                "find",
                "rescue",
                "infrared",
                "thermal",
                "operation"
            ]
        }
    }
}
